http://www.wfdenny.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Order before 1pm Monday-Friday for same day dispatch. Please be aware our couriers may experience delays due to higher parcel volumes.
Basket
Account My AccountCreate an Account Sign In
Menu PackagingFood PackagingBiodegradable ProductsCake Boxes, Boards and AcetatesPiping BagsCatering DisposablesColpac Packaging - WF DennyColpac Stagione Food Packaging RangeFood Produce Bags & NetsTakeaway & Hot Food ContainersBagsCarrier BagsFilm Fronted & All Film BagsPolythene BagsPaper BagsHygiene & Cleaning ProductsMail Order ItemsBubble Wrap & Pallet WrapMailing Sacks & Document WalletsTapes & DispensersPacking BoxesOffice StationerySheets & WrappingsFood Use WrappingsShop WrappingsTissue PaperSALE/Clearance PackagingPartywareHanukkah PartywareChristmas PartywareNew Year PartywareNew Year TablewareNew Year DecorationsNew Year Wearables & AccessoriesNew Year BalloonsBalloons & AccessoriesLatex BalloonsFoil BalloonsBubble BalloonsBalloon Arch KitsBalloon WeightsBalloon Ribbon ReelsBalloon PacksHelium Gas BottlesBalloon AccessoriesBalloon Strings and TailsThemed PartywareRoaring 20's Art Deco PartywareHawaiian Luau & Tropical Partyware70s Disco & 80s PartywareCasino & Cards PartywareFloral Tea PartyNavy & Gold Geode PartywareRose Gold Sparkling Fizz PartywareRose All Day PartywareDog PartyMexican Fiesta PartyGold Celebration PartyPink Celebration Party RangeRainbow PartywareUnion Jack & England PartywarePastel Celebrations PartywareSpecific Age PartywareAge 1 PartywareAge 2-5 PartywareAge 6-15 PartywareAge 16 And 17 PartywareAge 18 PartywareAge 21 PartywareAge 30 PartywareAge 40 PartywareAge 50 PartywareAge 60 PartywareAge 65 PartywareAge 70 PartywareAge 80 PartywareAge 90 PartywareAge 100 PartywareOccasion PartywareEngagement PartywareHen Party & Bridal Shower PartywareWedding PartywareAnniversary PartywareBaby Shower & Gender Reveal PartywareNew Baby PartywareChristening PartywareCommunion PartywareConfirmation PartywareCongratulations PartywareGet Well PartywareGraduation PartywareRetirement & Leaving Party PartywareWelcome PartywareSpecific Colour PartywareRose Gold PartywareWhite & Clear PartywareSilver PartywareGold PartywareBlack PartywareRed PartywareHot Pink PartywareBaby Pink PartywareOrange PartywareYellow PartywareLime Green PartywareForest Green PartywareBaby Blue PartywareCaribbean Blue PartywareRoyal Blue PartywareLilac PartywarePurple PartywareCream PartywareParty DecorationsDoor CurtainsHanging DecorationsInflatable Party DecorationsParty BannersFoil BannersLetter BannersThemed BannersBalloon BannersParty BuntingPaper DecorationsScene SettersSwirl DecorationsTable Centre PiecesTable Confetti & GemsTablewareCups Glasses & JugsCutleryDessert & Serving BowlsTablecovers & ClothsNapkinsPlatesSolid Colour PlatesPatterned And Themed PlatesBiodegradable PlatesPremium PlatesPlattersServing UtensilsCupcake StandsCake Boxes & DrumsDoyleysFoil Trays & RoastersBiodegradable TablewareChildren's Party Themes And ToysUnicorn PartywareDinosaur PartywareMermaid PartywareFootball PartywareGaming PartywareHarry Potter PartywarePeppa Pig PartywareJungle PartywarePirate PartywarePrincess PartywareFarmyard PartywareRainbow PartywareSpace And Galaxy PartywareAll Aboard Train PartywareToysGames & AccessoriesNoise MakersValue PacksParty AccessoriesBadgesBubblesCake CandlesGift Wrapping & Tissue PaperGlow in the Dark WearablesInflatablesInvitationsName Cards & Place HoldersParty BagsPhoto Booth PropsParty EssentialsParty Horns & BlowersParty
KitsParty WearablesParty PoppersSashesStrawsCake DecorationsParty Boxes & BagsColoured Meal BoxesPaper Party BagsPrinted Design Meal BoxesPinatasCandy Buffet & AccessoriesClearance Partyware Visit Our Store Account
Eco-friendly products
Over 90 years experience
A B2B | B2C company
Purchase in-store | online
Privacy Policy
This website ("website") is operated by W.F. Denny. This privacy policy only covers information collected at this website, and does not cover any information collected offline by W.F. Denny. All W.F. Denny websites are covered by this privacy policy.
The Information We Collect
Generally, you may browse the W.F. Denny website without providing any personally identifiable information. However, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information at various times and places on this website. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to access all parts of this website or participate in all of its features, pricing, and product selection.
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section. From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use. When you visit this website, our web server automatically collects anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses, and may collect general information concerning your location. We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.
How We Use The Information We Collect
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
A "web beacon" or "pixel tag" or "clear gif" is typically a one-pixel image, used to pass information from your computer or mobile device to a website.
We use cookies and web beacons to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to the website as well as to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the website you visited immediately before clicking to the W.F. Denny website. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. You can, of course, disable cookies and web beacons on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our website will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. We may also use web beacons, and other technologies, to help track whether our communications are reaching you, to measure their effectiveness, or to collect certain non-personal information about your computer, device, or browser in order to allow us to better design future communications to you.
We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and web beacons and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services, or data management. We call them our Customer Care Partners. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Customer Care Partners.
By using this website you're confirming that you're happy to accept our use of cookies.
Here you can find out more about how we use them.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or mobile or tablet when visiting certain websites. Cookies keep track of your movements on the site to track what’s in your shopping basket and provide functions to improve your shopping experience.
To order products on this site you need cookies enabled. Internet cookies are common and won’t cause any harm to your device. No personally identifiable information is stored within cookies therefore we recommend you leave these switched on.
What types of activity do we use cookies for?
Shopping Basket - Some cookies are essential during online transactions, e.g. to remember what products you have put in your shopping basket as you navigate to different pages on the website. These cookies are strictly necessary for the operation of the website.
User Experience - Cookies are used to remember your preferences on the site. These cookies are not shared with other websites.
Profiling - We use cookies to enable us to serve more targeted advertising to our customers on this website. By knowing your browsing habits we can show advertisements that are more targeted to your interests.
Video content - Flash cookies (or Local Shared Objects) are used to display video content using Adobe Flash Player.
Types of Cookies
There are two common types of cookies;
Session Cookie: Session cookies are created temporarily in your browser's subfolder while you're visiting a website. They allow a site to remember content from page to page, e.g. the shopping basket. These cookies expire when you leave the site or close the browser.
Persistent cookie: Persistent cookies remain on your computer and are activated again once you visit the website that created that particular cookie. A persistent cookie still has a lifespan which is set when the cookie is created. The cookie will disappear after this time.
Are cookies safe?
Yes, cookies are small text files. They can't look into your computer or read any personal information or other material on your hard drive. Cookies can't carry viruses or install anything harmful on your computer.
Why should I keep cookies switched on?
We would like you to keep cookies active on your computer during your visits to our website because parts of the site rely on them to work properly. For example, you will not be able to add any products to your basket if your cookies are disabled.
List of 1st Party Cookies Currently Set
The following list of cookies may have been set or read by us at some stage.
Cookie NameValueDescription
x8372ygjfr783ghj
290caf4c163c5451773329b9b83a72cc4b3d4560686462ec531c846121297b9b83a72cc4b3d4560686462ec531c84750caf4c163c5761
This stores an internal reference to the site you came to us from.
This allows us to track which sites have sent us traffic or sales for commissions or statistics.
oqough487hjkdnj
6d81215c163c5109414621b9b83a72cc4b3d4560686462ec531c84411783b9b83a72cc4b3d4560686462ec531c84b981215c163c5761
This stores an internal reference to your shopping basket.
This allows you to shop online with us.
iu398jkdjinnbb
yes
Stores whether you have consented to this website using cookies.
_gid
GA1.3.1974153469.1547477034
_ga
GA1.3.286956752.1547050065
PHPSESSID
af7l9t177bmg5vbvrg7mi7m6p1
Internal PHP (programming language) session ID. Unique to you.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and the information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Allows pages to be displayed more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are signed into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores your Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag that, indicates whether caching is on or off.
FRONTEND
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The last product you looked at.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to usecache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items you recently compared.
STF
Information on products you emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer authorized cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you recently looked at.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your wish list.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your wish list.
Online Account Registration
To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register on the W.F. Denny website. As a registered customer, you only have to enter your shipping addresses and billing information once; they will be securely stored with us for your future use. Using your name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information. If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to Sign Out when you finish shopping. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.
Emails
You will receive promotional emails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want to receiveemailfrom W.F. Denny or its affiliates you can click on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Please allow us 3 business days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request.
Acceptance
By using this website, you accept the policies set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Questions for W.F. Denny?
Contact Us
